barilliance.com 2019-08-09

# Privacy Policy - Barilliance

## Information Collected

We require customers who use selected services (collectively, the “Service”) to give us contact information, such as their name, company name, address, phone number, and e-mail address.

We may also email information regarding updates to the Service or company, and we might send a Customer Newsletter. Again, customers can opt out of receiving any communication by emailing support@Barilliance.com.

Except as stated at the time we request information, or as contemplated in this policy or the “Barilliance Service Agreement” or required by law, we do not disclose any personally identifiable information (including, without limitation, email addresses) that is provided by customers to third parties.

Customers of the Service will be using the site to host data and information (“hosted data”). The Service also includes connecting to customers’ databases and applications (“source data”) and extracting a copy of the source data that is then loaded into the Barilliance system. Barilliance will not review, share, distribute, print, or reference any hosted data or source data except as provided in this policy or in the Barilliance Master Subscription Agreement or as may be required by law, and except for the purposes of deploying, supporting or enhancing the service.

Of course, customers are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of their user registration and password.

Barilliance may collect certain information from visitors to the website and customers of the Service. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to constantly improve the quality of the website and the Service. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers and provide such information to third parties.

## Request of Information

On some pages of our website users have the option to register for various Barilliance services – e.g. newsletter, download of whitepapers, etc. – using data capture forms. These forms usually require the user’s name, email address, company, as well as other information that is necessary to provide the requested service. The user may choose to provide additional non-mandatory information that enables us to provide a more personalized service. To the extent it is permitted by applicable laws, we may also directly contact website users based on the information they have provided to promote Barilliance products. The users can object to the use of their data as described above at any time by emailing support@barilliance.com.

## Cookies

Alone, cookies do not identify you personally. They merely recognize your browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to Barilliance, such as responding to a promotional offer or opening an account, you remain anonymous to Barilliance.

Barilliance uses session cookies (cookies that exist only during an online session) containing encrypted information to allow the system to uniquely identify you while you are logged in to the Service. This information allows Barilliance to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies help us make sure you are who you say you are after you’ve logged in and are required in order to use the Barilliance application. Users who disable their Web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will not be able to successfully use our Service.

Third Party Cookies: We may engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to our website and customers of our service to help us administer the website and the Service and improve its quality. Such third parties may use cookies to help track visitor behavior.

## Shared Usage of Data

We reserve the right to share accumulated, general demographic data for statistical purposes with selected partners. These data do not contain any personally identifiable information.

## Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please note that Barilliance is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other websites to which we link.

## Contacts Under Sixteen Years of Age

Barilliance does not specifically target anyone under the age of sixteen. Persons under the age of sixteen are not permitted to use the Barilliance platform.

## Other Types of Information Gathering  

Occasionally our website gathers visitors’ data via temporary marketing activities such as webinars, free trial accounts, surveys, etc. Participation in these activities is on a voluntary basis, which allows the visitor to decide whether to disclose any personal data or not. Such data may include, but is not limited to, contact information (e.g. name, email, phone number) and demographic information (e.g. zip code, date of birth). The data will be used to provide the visitor with the service requested. Data gathered via surveys will be used for improving our website and services. Where explicit consent is given, data provided will also be used for Barilliance marketing communications, such as email and direct mail. The subscription details can be referenced on the form being filled. Further information can be found under the sub-header ‘Information Tracking and Usage’ within this policy.

## Correcting & Updating Your Information  

If customers need to update or change registration information they may do so by editing the user or company profile record. To update a User Profile or Company Profile, log on to Barilliance as an Administrator and perform the updates in the Administration area. To discontinue the Service and to have data returned, email support@Barilliance.com. Barilliance will respond to your correction or update request within at most 30 days from the date of your request.

## Email Marketing  

By subscribing to our email marketing, you will be the first to learn about new products, valuable tips and news as well as exclusive offers. After signing up you will receive a confirmation email with an activation link to start receiving the newsletter. Emails will be sent from or include the brand name 'Barilliance' within. Email sending frequency will vary. If you no longer wish to receive our emails you can unsubscribe at any time, simply by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the footer of any of our emails. Alternatively, consent can be withdrawn by emailing support@barilliance.com.

We use the email address specified during a purchase for direct marketing activities for our own similar products or services. These mailings are intended to inform you about the product(s) you have bought. If you do not wish to receive our product update communications any longer, you can unsubscribe from them at any time without costs other than the transmission costs pursuant to the basic tariffs being incurred in this regard. Unsubscription can simply be done by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the footer of any of our product update emails. Alternatively, consent can be withdrawn by emailing support@barilliance.com.

## Opt-Out Policy  

Barilliance offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering the Service, you change your mind about receiving information from us, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply send your request to support@Barilliance.com.

## External Service Providers  

For certain activities related to this website we have retained the services of external data processors (e.g. data centers). These service providers process data only in accordance with our instructions, are therefore also bound by this privacy policy, and are subject to our control. Under no circumstances may these service providers use any data that are collected and processed in relation to this website for their own purposes.

## ​Changes to this Statement  

Barilliance will notify its Clients via email if we make any changes to our Privacy Policy. Any new policy will be posted on our site at least thirty (30) days prior to its taking effect.
